Digital Collections and Archives Records UA069
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Digital objects, 1662 -- 2015; 2000 -- 2004; UA069.005; 542 Digital Object(s)
  - The Old Court Suburb, or Memorials of Kensington, Regal, Critical, and Anecdotical, Volume II, 1855; UA069.005.DO.00052; Hunt, Leigh
  - Essays and Orations, Read and Delivered at the Royal College of Physicians to which is Added an Account of the Opening of the Tomb of King Charles, 1833; UA069.005.DO.00053; Halford, Henry
  - Old London Bridge, A Romance of the Sixteenth Century, 1860; UA069.005.DO.00055; Rodwell, G Herbert
    London (England)--History--16th century--Fiction
  - Homes of the London Poor, 1875; UA069.005.DO.00056; Hill, Miss Octavia
    Poor--England--London; Working class--Dwellings; Charity organization
  - Britannia: or a Geographical description of the Kingdoms of England, Scotland, and Ireland, with the Isles and Territories thereto belonging., 1687; UA069.005.DO.00057; Blome, Richard
  - Walks in London, vol. I, 1878; UA069.005.DO.00058; Hare, Augustus J. C.
  - Walks in London, vol. 2, 1878; UA069.005.DO.00059; Hare, Augustus J. C.
  - Old and New London, A Narrative of its History, its People and its Places. Illustrated with Numerous Engravings from the Most Authentic Sources. vol I, 1872 -- 1878; UA069.005.DO.00060; Thornbury, Walter
  - Old and New London, A Narrative of its History, its People and its Places. Illustrated with Numerous Engravings from the Most Authentic Sources. vol 2, 1872 -- 1878; UA069.005.DO.00061; Thornbury, Walter
  - Old and New London, A Narrative of its History, its People and its Places. Illustrated with Numerous Engravings from the Most Authentic Sources. vol 3, 1872 -- 1878; UA069.005.DO.00062; Walford, Edward
  - Old and New London, A Narrative of its History, its People and its Places. Illustrated with Numerous Engravings from the Most Authentic Sources. vol 4, 1872 -- 1878; UA069.005.DO.00063; Walford, Edward
  - Old and New London, A Narrative of its History, its People and its Places. Illustrated with Numerous Engravings from the Most Authentic Sources. vol 5, 1872 -- 1878; UA069.005.DO.00064; Walford, Edward
  - Old and New London, A Narrative of its History, its People and its Places. Illustrated with Numerous Engravings from the Most Authentic Sources. vol 6, 1872 -- 1878; UA069.005.DO.00065; Walford, Edward
  - The History and Antiquities of London, Westminster, Southwark, and Parts Adjacent, vol. 1, 1827; UA069.005.DO.00066; Allen, Thomas
    London (England); History; Antiquities
  - The History and Antiquities of London, Westminster, Southwark, and Parts Adjacent, vol. 2, 1828; UA069.005.DO.00067; Allen, Thomas
    London (England)--History; Antiquities
  - The History and Antiquities of London, Westminster, Southwark, and Parts Adjacent, vol. 3, 1827; UA069.005.DO.00068; Allen, Thomas
  - The History and Antiquities of London, Westminster, Southwark, and Parts Adjacent, vol. 4, 1827; UA069.005.DO.00069; Allen, Thomas
  - London: A Pilgrimage, 1890; UA069.005.DO.00070; Jerrold, Blanchard
    London (England)--Description and Travel; London (England)--Social life and customs
  - London Labour and the London Poor, volume 2, 1851; UA069.005.DO.00078; Mayhew, Henry
  - London Labour and the London Poor, volume 3, 1851; UA069.005.DO.00079; Mayhew, Henry
  - London Labour and the London Poor, extra volume, 1851; UA069.005.DO.00080; Mayhew, Henry
  - Athletic Rosters of Tufts University, 2003; UA069.005.DO.00083; Kenny, Maura; Sauer, Anne; Crowley, Zachary E.
    The Athletics Rosters of Tufts University is the result of a project to collect and record the participants in organized athletics at Tufts University. The names contained in these rosters were compiled from the records of the Department of Physical Education/Athletics and particularly the Athletic Association Meeting Minutes and team files, as well as publications such as student newspapers, the Tuftonian, the Brown and Blue, and the Jumbo Book.
    Athletics; Dept. of Phys. Ed./Athletics; Tufts University
  - Light on the Hill, Volume II, 1986; UA069.005.DO.00084; Miller, Russell
    Light on the Hill, the second volume of the history of Tufts University, was published in 1986, covering the years from 1952 to 1986. This doucument was created from the 1986 edition of Light on the Hill, Volume II.
    Tufts University -- History; Tufts University
    - Rocky Carzo with Bob Bass and Rich Giachetti, UA069.005.DO.00084.00002
      Football; Carzo, Rocco "Rocky"; Giachetti, Rich; Bass, Rob
    - Field Hockey, UA069.005.DO.00084.00003
      Field Hockey; Athletic fields; Athletics
    - Woman with Jumbo, UA069.005.DO.00084.00004
      Building sites; Animals
    - The Dental Health Sciences Tower in Boston, UA069.005.DO.00084.00006
    - The Sackler Center for Health Communications, dedicated in February 1986, UA069.005.DO.00084.00007
    - The Cabot Intercultural Center, UA069.005.DO.00084.00008
      Building sites; Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy
    - The Elizabeth van Huysen Mayer Campus Center, UA069.005.DO.00084.00009
  - Wastewater Engineering and Management Plan for Boston Harbor, 1976; UA069.005.DO.00085; Metcalf & Eddy, Inc.
    Wastewater Engineering and Management Plan for Boston Harbor is from the Mystic River Watershed Association
    Mystic River Watershed Association
  - The Mystic River Basin Report Action Handbook and Summary, 1977; UA069.005.DO.00086; Metropolitan Area Planning Council
    The Mystic River Basin Report Action Handbook and Summary is from the Mystic River Watershed Association
  - Blensdorf Family Letters, 1934 -- 1948; UA069.005.DO.00087; Kenny, Maura
    The letters of the Blensdorf family were selected from the Donald and Charolotte MacJannet Papers at the Digital Collections and Archives to better illustrate the history of Donald and Chalrotte MacJannet, as well as providing historical insight to the time period the letters represent. The letters have been rearranged into chronological order from their existing order within the collection to better facilitate understanding. Letters were all handwritten and as such extremely hard to read in some cases. Best approximations were made as to words by the translators.
    Letters (correspondence); MacJannet, Charlotte Blensdorf
  - MacJannet Legacy: The MacJannet School, 2003; UA069.005.DO.00088; Kenny, Maura
    The history of the MacJannet School
    MacJannet, Charlotte Blensdorf; MacJannet School (French Vacation School)
  - The MacJannet Camp, 2003; UA069.005.DO.00089; Kenny, Maura
    The history of the MacJannet Camp in Talloires, France compiled from information in the Donald and Charlotte MacJannet Papers.
    MacJannet, Charlotte Blensdorf; MacJannet Camp
  - History of Tufts College, 1854-1896, UA069.005.DO.00091; Start, Alaric Bertrand
    Published by the Class of 1897. The original contains appendices with a directory of alumni, the college catalog, and the college charter. These were not included in this addition.
    - Ballou Hall, UA069.005.DO.00091.00001; Start, Alaric Bertrand
      Building sites; Trees
    - West Hall, UA069.005.DO.00091.00002; Start, Alaric Bertrand
    - Barnum Museum, UA069.005.DO.00091.00003; Start, Alaric Bertrand
    - Metcalf Hall, UA069.005.DO.00091.00004; Start, Alaric Bertrand
    - Theta Delta Chi Charge-House, UA069.005.DO.00091.00005; Start, Alaric Bertrand
      Building sites; Trees; Fraternities
    - Commons Building, UA069.005.DO.00091.00006; Start, Alaric Bertrand
    - Paige Hall and Miner Hall, UA069.005.DO.00091.00007; Start, Alaric Bertrand
    - Benjamin F. Tweed, UA069.005.DO.00091.00008; Start, Alaric Bertrand
      People; Men; Professors; Faculty; Tweed, Benjamin Franklin
    - Jerome Schneider, UA069.005.DO.00091.00009; Start, Alaric Bertrand
      People; Men; Professors; Faculty; Schneider, Jerome
    - Hermon A Dearborn, UA069.005.DO.00091.00010; Start, Alaric Bertrand
      People; Men; Professors; Faculty; Dearborn, Heman A.
    - Moses T. Brown, UA069.005.DO.00091.00011; Start, Alaric Bertrand
      People; Men; Professors; Faculty; Brown, Moses True
    - Benjamin G. Brown, UA069.005.DO.00091.00012; Start, Alaric Bertrand
      People; Men; Professors; Faculty; Brown, Benjamin G.
    - Charles E. Fay, UA069.005.DO.00091.00013; Start, Alaric Bertrand
      People; Men; Professors; Faculty; Fay, Charles Ernest
    - Stephen M. Pitman, UA069.005.DO.00091.00014; Start, Alaric Bertrand
      People; Men; Professors; Faculty; Pitman, Stephen M
    - Arthur M. Comey, UA069.005.DO.00091.00015; Start, Alaric Bertrand
      People; Men; Professors; Faculty; Comey, Arthur M.
    - William L. Hopper, UA069.005.DO.00091.00016; Start, Alaric Bertrand
      People; Men; Professors; Faculty; Hopper, William L.
    - David L. Maulsby, UA069.005.DO.00091.00017; Start, Alaric Bertrand
      People; Men; Professors; Faculty; Maulsby, David Lee
    - Arthur Michael, UA069.005.DO.00091.00018; Start, Alaric Bertrand
      People; Men; Professors; Faculty; Michael, Arthur
    - Frank E. Sanborn, UA069.005.DO.00091.00019; Start, Alaric Bertrand
      People; Men; Professors; Faculty; Sanborn, Frank E.
    - Edwin A Start, UA069.005.DO.00091.00020; Start, Alaric Bertrand
      People; Men; Professors; Faculty; Start, Edwin Augustus
    - Frank T. Daniels, UA069.005.DO.00091.00021; Start, Alaric Bertrand
      People; Men; Professors; Faculty; Daniels, Frank
    - Horatio W. Myrick, Howard H. Higbee, Frank G. Wren, Thomas Whitemore, George H. Furbish, John E Bucher, UA069.005.DO.00091.00022; Start, Alaric Bertrand
      People; Men; Professors; Faculty; Wren, Frank G.; Higbee, Howard H.; Myrick, Horatio W.; Whitemore, Thomas; Furbish, George H.; Bucher, John E.
    - William G. Tousey, UA069.005.DO.00091.00023; Start, Alaric Bertrand
      People; Men; Professors; Faculty; Tousey, William G.
    - George M. Harmon, UA069.005.DO.00091.00024; Start, Alaric Bertrand
      People; Men; Professors; Faculty; Harmon, George
    - Anson B. Curtis, UA069.005.DO.00091.00025; Start, Alaric Bertrand
      People; Men; Professors; Faculty; Curtis, Anson B.
    - Warren S. Woodbridge, UA069.005.DO.00091.00026; Start, Alaric Bertrand
      People; Men; Professors; Faculty; Woodbridge, Warren S.
    - Charles P.Thayer, UA069.005.DO.00091.00027; Start, Alaric Bertrand
      People; Men; Professors; Faculty; Thayer, Charles Paine
  - A History of Music in Tufts College, 1869-1945, 1886 -- 1947; UA069.005.DO.00092; Hersey, Harry Adams
    This document was created from the 1947 edition of A History of Music in Tufts College.
    - Leo Rich Lewis, 1947; UA069.005.DO.00092.00001; Hersey, Harry Adams
      This doucument was created from the 1947 edition of A History of Music in Tufts College.
      People; Men; Lewis, Leo R.
    - Rally Cry, UA069.005.DO.00092.00002
      Music
    - Rally Cry continued, UA069.005.DO.00092.00003
    - Program of the first Glee Club Concert on the Hill., 1886; UA069.005.DO.00092.00004
    - President Elmer Hewitt Capen, UA069.005.DO.00092.00005
      This doucument was created from the 1947 edition of A History of Music in Tufts College. No Date available
      People; Men; Capen, Elmer Hewitt
    - Top floor, Goddard Gymnasium., UA069.005.DO.00092.00006
      Offices; Furniture
    - The Music House, UA069.005.DO.00092.00007
      Building sites; Trees; Aerial views
    - Tufts College Glee Club, Season 1889-90, 1889 -- 1890; UA069.005.DO.00092.00008
      People; Music; Clubs; Students; Student activities
    - Tufts College Glee and Banjo Club, Season 1890-91., 1890 -- 1891; UA069.005.DO.00092.00009
    - Tufts College Glee and Mandolin Club, Season 1891-92, 1891 -- 1892; UA069.005.DO.00092.00010
    - Tufts College Glee and Mandolin Club, Season 1893-94, 1893 -- 1894; UA069.005.DO.00092.00011
    - Tufts Glee, Mandolin and Guitar Clubs, 1895-96, 1895 -- 1896; UA069.005.DO.00092.00012
    - Tufts Glee, Mandolin and Guitar Clubs, 1897-98, 1897 -- 1898; UA069.005.DO.00092.00013
    - Tufts Glee, Mandolin and Guitar Clubs, 1899-00., 1800 -- 1899; UA069.005.DO.00092.00014
    - Tufts Glee, Mandolin and Guitar Clubs, 1902-'03, 1902 -- 1903; UA069.005.DO.00092.00015
    - Tufts Glee, Mandolin and Guitar Clubs, 1904-05., 1904 -- 1905; UA069.005.DO.00092.00016
    - Tufts Glee, Mandolin and Guitar Clubs, 1905-06., 1905 -- 1906; UA069.005.DO.00092.00017
    - Tufts Glee, Mandolin and Guitar Clubs, 1909-10., 1909 -- 1910; UA069.005.DO.00092.00018
      People; Music; Clubs; Students; Student activities; Trees
    - Tufts College Musical Clubs, 1914-15, 1914 -- 1915; UA069.005.DO.00092.00019
    - Tufts College Musical Clubs, 1919-20, 1919 -- 1920; UA069.005.DO.00092.00020
    - Tufts College Musical Clubs, 1921-22, 1921 -- 1922; UA069.005.DO.00092.00021
      People; Music; Clubs; Students; Student activities; Trees; Instruments
    - Tufts College Musical Clubs, 1922-23, 1922 -- 1923; UA069.005.DO.00092.00022
      People; Music; Clubs; Students; Student activities; Instruments
    - Semi-Centennial Rehearsal Group, Tufts College, 1905 -- 1936; UA069.005.DO.00092.00023
    - College Choir, 1899-00, 1800 -- 1899; UA069.005.DO.00092.00024
    - The Rose and Ring, 1912; UA069.005.DO.00092.00025
      People; Theater; Clubs; Students; Student activities
    - Program for The Rose and the Ring, UA069.005.DO.00092.00026
    - Program for Jack and the Baked Bean Stalk, UA069.005.DO.00092.00027
    - Princess Ida, UA069.005.DO.00092.00028
    - Scenes from Princess Ida, UA069.005.DO.00092.00029
    - Jumbonians, 1926-27, 1926 -- 1927; UA069.005.DO.00092.00030
    - Banjo Club 1889-90, 1889 -- 1890; UA069.005.DO.00092.00031
    - Mandolin Club 1892-93, 1892 -- 1893; UA069.005.DO.00092.00032
    - Mandolin and Glee Clubs, 1898-99, 1892 -- 1893; UA069.005.DO.00092.00033
    - Mandolin Club, 1916-17, 1916 -- 1917; UA069.005.DO.00092.00034
    - First Informal Sing on the Reservoir Terrace, 1906 -- 1920; UA069.005.DO.00092.00035
    - The Alma Mater Piano in Leo Lewis' room in West Hall, UA069.005.DO.00092.00036
      Interior views; Music; Instruments; Buildings; Furniture
    - First complete draft of Alma Mater, 1898; UA069.005.DO.00092.00037
      Documents
    - Professor Lewis conducting Tufts Night at Pops, UA069.005.DO.00092.00038
      Music; Instruments; Student activities; Lewis, Leo R.
    - Professor Lewis conducting Tufts Night at Pops, UA069.005.DO.00092.00039
    - Bowen Chimes, UA069.005.DO.00092.00040
      Bells; Exterior views
    - Illustrations from Comus program, UA069.005.DO.00092.00041
      People; Illustrations
    - Cut of page 1 of Old Fortunatus program, UA069.005.DO.00092.00042
      Programs
    - Cut of back page of Old Fortunatus program, UA069.005.DO.00092.00043
    - In the record library, UA069.005.DO.00092.00044
      Interior views; Music; Libraries; Lewis, Leo R.
    - 'Last sing' in Goddard Gymnasium, UA069.005.DO.00092.00045
      Interior views; Students; Student activities; Lewis, Leo R.
    - Professor Lewis at classroom organ, UA069.005.DO.00092.00046
      Interior views; Rooms; Lewis, Leo R.
    - Professor Lewis in classroom, UA069.005.DO.00092.00047
    - Professor Lewis referees the no decision bout between the Glee Club and the dish-clattering waitresses, UA069.005.DO.00092.00048
      Illustrations; Cartoons; Lewis, Leo R.
    - As Santa Claus, UA069.005.DO.00092.00049
      Interior views; Santa Claus; Building sites; Lewis, Leo R.
  - A Survey of London, 1908; UA069.005.DO.00093; Stow, John
  - Here and There at Tufts, 1907; UA069.005.DO.00094; Doane, Lewis
    Here and There at Tufts, was published by the class of 1909 as an early form of a yearbook. The text includes photographs and histories of academic buildings, dormitories, former deans and presidents, classrooms, fraternities, athletic teams, and student organizations.
  - Another Light on the Hill: A History of Black Students at Tufts, 1900-the Present, 1960 -- 2002; UA069.005.DO.00095; Gill, Gerald R.
    Article on the history of black students at Tufts, accompanies exhibit
    Black people; Tufts University -- History; Gill, Gerald R.; Tufts University
    - Essence, 1998; UA069.005.DO.00095.00001
      From Prof. Gerald Gill's personal collection; Female singing group
      Black people; Students; Student activities; Singers; Women; Tufts University
    - Woolworth's Boycott, 1960; UA069.005.DO.00095.00002
      From the personal collection of Gerald Gill; Students passing out leaflets in Davis Sq. promoting boycott of Woolworth's
      Black people; Students; Boycott; Tufts University
    - Pan-African Alliance, 2001 -- 2002; UA069.005.DO.00095.00003
      From the personal collection of Gerald Gill; Three student members of the Pan-African Alliance
      Black people; Students; Student activities; Clubs; Tufts University
    - African Student Organization, 2001 -- 2002; UA069.005.DO.00095.00004
      From the personal collection of Gerald Gill; Two female students holding African Student Organization (A.S.O.) banner
      Black people; Women; Student activities; Clubs; Students; Tufts University
    - TCU Senator Myra Frazier, 1902 -- 1987; UA069.005.DO.00095.00005
      From the personal collection of Gerald Gill; Tufts Community Union Senator and student, Myra Frazier
      Black people; Women; Student activities; Politics; Frazier, Myra; Tufts University
    - Homecoming King and Queen, 1983 -- 1984; UA069.005.DO.00095.00006
      From the personal collection of Gerald Gill
      Black people; Students; Student activities; Events; Tufts University
    - Ain't Misbehavin', 1902 -- 1990; UA069.005.DO.00095.00008
      Program cover for Black Theatre Co. production
      Black people; Drama; Students; Student activities; Plays; Playwrights; O'Hara, Robert; Simms, Heather; Tufts University
  - Academic Achievements and Sporting Accomplishments: The History of Black Male and Female Athletes at Tufts, 1900-Present, 2003; UA069.005.DO.00096; Gill, Gerald R.
    Article on the history of black student athletes at Tufts; accompaniment to ALH exhibit
    Black people; Tufts University -- History; Athletics; Students; Gill, Gerald R.; Tufts University
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: How the Information Revolution is Transforming Our World, 1992; UA069.005.DO.00097; Wriston, Walter B.
    "Twilight of Sovereignty: How the Information Revolution is Transforming our World" is a compilation of speeches by Walter B. Wriston discussing the information technology.
    Information technology; Wriston, Walter B.; Charles Scribner's Sons
    - The Twilight of Sovereignty Book Jacket, 1992; UA069.005.DO.00097.00001
      This image is the front cover of the book jacket for the publication, "The Twilight of Sovereignty: How the Information Revolution is Transforming Our World ."
  - Inaugural Address at the Opening of Tufts College, August 22, 1855., UA069.005.DO.00098; Ballou, Hosea
    Inaugural Address by Hosea Ballou at the opening of Tufts College in 1855.
    Ballou, Hosea, 2d; Tufts College
  - Athletic Rosters of Tufts University for the year 1864, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00099; Kenny, Maura; Sauer, Anne; Crowley, Zachary E.
    Athletics; Baseball; Rowing; Dept. of Phys. Ed./Athletics; Tufts University
  - Athletic Rosters of Tufts University for the year 1865, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00100; Kenny, Maura; Sauer, Anne; Crowley, Zachary E.
    Athletics; Baseball; Rowing; Crew; Dept. of Phys. Ed./Athletics; Tufts University
  - Athletic Rosters of Tufts University for the year 1867, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00101; Kenny, Maura; Sauer, Anne; Crowley, Zachary E.
  - Athletic Rosters of Tufts University for the year 1868, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00102; Kenny, Maura; Sauer, Anne; Crowley, Zachary E.
  - Athletic Rosters of Tufts University for the year 1869, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00103; Kenny, Maura; Sauer, Anne; Crowley, Zachary E.
  - Athletic Rosters of Tufts University for the year 1870, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00104; Kenny, Maura; Sauer, Anne; Crowley, Zachary E.
    Athletics; Baseball; Crew; Dept. of Phys. Ed./Athletics; Tufts University
  - Athletic Rosters of Tufts University for the year 1871, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00105; Kenny, Maura; Sauer, Anne; Crowley, Zachary E.
    Athletics; Baseball; Football; Crew; Dept. of Phys. Ed./Athletics; Tufts University
  - Athletic Rosters of Tufts University for the year 1873, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00106; Kenny, Maura; Sauer, Anne; Crowley, Zachary E.
    Athletics; Baseball; Dept. of Phys. Ed./Athletics; Tufts University
  - Athletic Rosters of Tufts University for the year 1874, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00107; Kenny, Maura; Sauer, Anne; Crowley, Zachary E.
    Athletics; Baseball; Fencing; Football; Dept. of Phys. Ed./Athletics; Tufts University
  - Athletic Rosters of Tufts University for the year 1875, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00108; Kenny, Maura; Sauer, Anne; Crowley, Zachary E.
  - Athletic Rosters of Tufts University for the year 1876, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00109; Kenny, Maura; Sauer, Anne; Crowley, Zachary E.
    Athletics; Football; Dept. of Phys. Ed./Athletics; Tufts University
  - Athletic Rosters of Tufts University for the year 1878, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00110; Kenny, Maura; Sauer, Anne; Crowley, Zachary E.
  - Athletic Rosters of Tufts University for the year 1879, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00111; Kenny, Maura; Sauer, Anne; Crowley, Zachary E.
    Athletics; Baseball; Football; Dept. of Phys. Ed./Athletics; Tufts University
  - Athletic Rosters of Tufts University for the year 1887, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00112; Kenny, Maura; Sauer, Anne; Crowley, Zachary E.
  - Athletic Rosters of Tufts University for the year 1888, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00113; Kenny, Maura; Sauer, Anne; Crowley, Zachary E.
    Athletics; Baseball; Tennis; Yachts; Football; Dept. of Phys. Ed./Athletics; Tufts University
  - Athletic Rosters of Tufts University for the year 1889, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00114; Kenny, Maura; Sauer, Anne; Crowley, Zachary E.
    Athletics; Baseball; Football; Yachts; Tennis; Dept. of Phys. Ed./Athletics; Tufts University
  - Athletic Rosters of Tufts University for the year 1890, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00115; Kenny, Maura; Sauer, Anne; Crowley, Zachary E.
    Athletics; Baseball; Football; Tennis; Dept. of Phys. Ed./Athletics; Tufts University
  - Athletic Rosters of Tufts University for the year 1891, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00116; Kenny, Maura; Sauer, Anne; Crowley, Zachary E.
    Athletics; Baseball; Tennis; Football; Dept. of Phys. Ed./Athletics; Tufts University
  - Athletic Rosters of Tufts University for the year 1892, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00117; Kenny, Maura; Sauer, Anne; Crowley, Zachary E.
  - Athletic Rosters of Tufts University for the year 1893, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00118; Kenny, Maura; Sauer, Anne; Crowley, Zachary E.
  - Athletic Rosters of Tufts University for the year 1894, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00119; Kenny, Maura; Sauer, Anne; Crowley, Zachary E.
  - Athletic Rosters of Tufts University for the year 1899, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00120; Kenny, Maura; Sauer, Anne; Crowley, Zachary E.
  - Athletic Rosters of Tufts University for the year 1900, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00121; Kenny, Maura; Sauer, Anne; Crowley, Zachary E.
  - Athletic Rosters of Tufts University for the year 1913, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00122; Kenny, Maura; Sauer, Anne; Crowley, Zachary E.
    Athletics; Track; Tennis; Baseball; Football; Dept. of Phys. Ed./Athletics; Tufts University
  - Athletic Rosters of Tufts University for the year 1914, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00123; Kenny, Maura; Sauer, Anne; Crowley, Zachary E.
    Athletics; Baseball; Track; Tennis; Football; Dept. of Phys. Ed./Athletics; Tufts University
  - Athletic Rosters of Tufts University for the year 1915, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00124; Kenny, Maura; Sauer, Anne; Crowley, Zachary E.
    Athletics; Baseball; Football; Track; Dept. of Phys. Ed./Athletics; Tufts University
  - Athletic Rosters of Tufts University for the year 1916, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00125; Kenny, Maura; Sauer, Anne; Crowley, Zachary E.